When you find that one person
who connects you to the world...
...you become someone different.
Someone better.
When that person is taken from you...
...what do you become then?
Whatever you wanna do, you know? Unh.
What? Hmm?
What, where did you get that, in a cereal
box? Huh? You wanna see a real gun?
Forget you.
Every punk is carrying. That's why your
father wanted us to take the car home.
Relax.
Picking up new hardware next week.
Restore a little order.
Besides, when we take the car,
we don't get to meet new friends.
Like this guy.
In order to continue OpenSubtitles.org
subtitles service you need to Log In
You bring enough
for the whole group?
Time to teach you about sharing.
I'll need a statement from the bum.
Which hospital did they take him to?
Declined treatment.
We got video on it though.
You know,
you could've done me a favor...
...and let those guys
land a couple more punches.
Question for you.
Looking at that tape, I'd say
you spent some time in the service.
I did.
Army.
Two tours in Iraq.
But you don't learn how to fight like that
in the regular army.
So, what were you?
Special Forces? Delta?
I'm Carter. You didn't give us a name.
You know, it's funny.
Best parts of your life...
...you don't need a name.
You get to be "Dad,"
"sweetheart," "pal. "
Seems like the only time you need
a name now is when you're in trouble.
So am I in trouble?
I don't know. You tell me.
You're the one living on the street.
You're not from here, are you?
What, you're just passing through?
I came to find an old friend.
Yeah, making that transition back
can be tough.
Some guys I knew got a little lost.
That disconnect between
what they were trained to do...
...and what they were expected to do
when they got home.
Some of them just
needed a little help adjusting.
You need some help?
Of course, some other guys I knew...
...they had done so many evil things...
...they felt
like they needed the punishment.
That sound more like your story, "pal"?
Excuse me for a second.
I'm here for my client.
Wow. Wow, wow.
Your guy's prints were found in half
a dozen crime scenes over the years.
Open warrants
in four different countries.
Missing Persons here in Queens,
'07, three guys disappeared.
Who you got down there, Carter?
The angel of death?
I appreciate the help, counselor.
But who's picking up the tab?
Our employer
wants to have a word with you.
Do I owe you money?
Because I'm, uh, running a little short
at the moment.
You don't owe me anything, Mr. Reese.
That's the name you prefer, isn't it?
I know you've had several.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna tell anybody about you.
You don't know anything about me.
I know exactly everything about you,
Mr. Reese.
I know about the work you used to do
for the government.
I know about the doubts
you came to have about that work.
I know that the government, along
with everybody else, thinks you're dead.
I know you've spent the last couple of
months trying to drink yourself to death.
I know you're contemplating
more efficient ways to do it.
Which would be a shame.
So you see,
knowledge is not my problem.
Doing something
with that knowledge...
...that's where you'd come in.
Who sent you?
Nobody sent me.
You can call me Mr. Finch.
I think you and I
can help one another.
I don't think you need a psychiatrist
or a support group or pills.
What do I need?
You need a purpose.
More specifically, you need a job.
Eight million people.
You know what they all have
in common?
None of them knows
what happens next.
Good things, maybe.
But for some of them, not so good.
Someone is murdered in New York City
every 18 hours. It's like Musical Chairs.
At the end of the day,
one of these people will be gone.
Bad things happen to people
every day.
- You can't stop that.
- What if you could?
Not things that happen
in the heat of the moment.
But so many crimes are planned
days, weeks in advance.
What if you could stop those?
Let me guess...
...you're a psychic.
Ha, ha. No psychic, no magic.
None of that.
It's funny, when I was a kid...
...I wanted a jet pack,
I wanted a summer house on Mars.
Then I realized I was living in
the Information Age.
This was a shocking disappointment
to me...
...until I realized
how revolutionary it was.
All of us are leaving a trail
of information in our wake.
Most of it's useless.
There's something hidden
in all that mess.
A faint outline of things to come.
The right person in the right place
with the right information...
...could change everything.
This is the problem I have, Mr. Reese...
...I've got a list.
A list of people who are about
to be involved in very bad situations.
Murders, kidnappings.
- Where did you get this list?
- Can't tell you, you'll have to trust me.
The people that are on my list, they have
no idea that anything's about to happen.
Most of them are just ordinary people.
Like who?
- Like her.
- Thank you.
Her name is Diane Hansen.
And this week,
she's at the top of my list.
Think something bad
is gonna happen involving her?
It's not that simple.
I don't know exactly what's gonna
happen or what her role in it is.
She might be the victim.
She could be the perpetrator.
All I know is that she is involved.
I want you to follow her.
Figure out what's gonna happen.
And stop it from happening.
Why not call the police?
If anybody knew I had this list,
it would be...
...problematic.
You would name your own salary,
expenses, whatever you need.
So, what do you think?
I think you're a bored rich guy.
I think that woman's your ex-wife
or someone you rode in an elevator with.
Either way, I think I'm done.
Police are looking for
a homeless man for further questioning.
The unidentified man
was originally believed...
...to be the victim
of a violent assault on a subway.
But now police consider the man
a person of interest...
...in a number of crimes nationwide.
Hey, sweetheart, what's wrong?
Jessica, what's wrong?
You need to understand, Mr. Reese.
The information I have is incomplete.
But it's never wrong.
You need to know
what it would be like to be forced...
...to listen to someone get murdered
and not be able to do anything about it.
Shut up!
Rick, no!
Kill 138.7, X-ray.
Twelve, August, 2008, 1:37 a.m.
Too late.
This recording is three years old.
A woman murdered in this room
by her husband.
For the insurance.
You were too late for her.
Just like you were too late
for your friend Jessica.
You were halfway around the world
when she was killed.
- What the hell do you know about it?
- It's the truth.
You left the government
because they lied. I never will.
A man with your skills
could make a lot of money...
...in this world but you don't do it.
I think all you ever wanted to do
is protect people.
That's a wiretap recording.
NSA or FISA. Government.
- But you're not government.
- No, I'm not.
I guess you could call me
a concerned third party.
You couldn't have saved this woman.
Or your friend.
But you could have
if you had known in time.
That's the other thing I'm offering you.
A chance to be there in time.
It's not too late for her.
You could help me stop
what's about to happen.
The question is, will you?
Diane Hansen.
Grew up in Detroit.
Moved to the city after law school.
Single.
- Does she have any enemies?
One or two.
She's an assistant district attorney.
The best conviction record
in her department.
Great. Nice short list
of possible suspects.
We have no idea when this bad thing
might happen, huh?
Could be in a week,
could be five minutes.
That's why we need to learn
as much as we can about her.
- How do you intend to begin?
- The slow way.
Cultivate a relationship.
Engineering situations
over weeks, months...
...to allow you to earn the asset's trust.
And the fast way?
Break into her home
and go through all her stuff.
What is this place?
The decline of Western civilization.
The city closed half its libraries.
Budget cuts.
This building was sold
to a bank that I control...
...which promptly
declared bankruptcy.
So the property is in a kind of limbo.
It doesn't exist.
Neither do you.
I did a little digging.
I recognize, Mr. Reese,
that there is a disparity...
...between how much I know about you
and how much you know about me.
I know you'll be trying to close that gap
as quickly as possible.
But I should tell you
I'm a really private person.
What have you found out about
our Ms. Hansen?
Well, she's squeaky-clean.
No debts, no attachments.
But she is taking ulcer medication,
sleeping pills...
...so she's scared or stressed
about something.
Assuming she's the target,
I'm going through her work e-mails...
...case files, looking for
anyone who stands out.
I've got picture on her.
But I need sound.
I could hack her cell phone...
...use the microphone to listen in,
GPS to track her.
But that takes gear
that's a little hard to come by.
Thought you might need that.
- So I built one.
- Oh.
"Good with computers. "
Driver's licenses.
Credit cards. Six cover identities.
Funds to be replenished
through a proxy corporation.
Just like when you were
with the agency.
When I was with the agency...
...I knew who was picking up the tab.
This is your list?
- The list?
- Yup.
But you don't get names, do you?
These are Social Security numbers...
...and each of them map out
to a violent crime.
- And all of these numbers represent...
- Lost chances.
I could be more help if you'd tell me
where you're getting these numbers.
It doesn't matter where. What you need
to know is that the next number is hers.
Trust works both ways, Finch.
If telling me where you're getting these
numbers would put your life at risk...
It would put a lot more people
than just me at risk.
And I'd say trusting an alcoholic
ex-government hitman...
...is a greater challenge
than trusting a middle-aged cripple.
I have one more address
for you to check out tonight.
Okay, Mr. Finch.
- What am I doing here?
Sleeping.
You have plenty to do tomorrow.
What are you talking about?
Who lives here?
You do, Mr. Reese.
Any luck finding Paul Bunyan?
Turns out "bearded loner"
covers a high percentage...
...of the homeless population.
Oh, thanks.
Wait, is this
the Missing Persons file from '07?
Yes, ma'am.
- This is all they had?
Yep.
Given Hansen's job,
we've got hundreds of people...
...who could be holding a grudge...
...so I'm starting with the people she's
worried about. I cut the list to three.
The first is Lawrence Pope,
the man Hansen is currently prosecuting.
When we got there,
the scene was, uh, colorful.
Five dead.
One of them had managed to crawl
10 feet to a phone to dial 911...
...despite the fact that this drug-slinging
piece of trash shot him in the gut.
- Your Honor.
- Pardon me, Your Honor.
Despite the fact that this
drug-slinging piece of trash...
...allegedly shot him in the gut.
The person who made that call
was Germaine Salts.
- And he was friends with the defendant?
Yeah, they were all friends.
We figure that's how Pope knew
the deal was going down.
Turns out career criminals
don't make trustworthy friends.
Detective Fusco,
when you interviewed Mr. Pope...
...what did he tell you in his defense?
He said if he'd shot the poor bastard...
...he would've shot him in the head,
quote, "Same as I always do," unquote.
Said he wouldn't have left him there
half dead, blubbering for his girlfriend.
No more questions, Your Honor.
Detective...
...you went a little off script
in your testimony.
You never told me
about that conversation...
...and it could clear Pope's name.
What's it matter, we got the guy.
It matters because
it's my job to make sure...
...the wrong people don't go to jail.
Remember?
Excuse me, I thought
we were on the same team.
You got time to talk?
I could buy you dinner?
- Busy. Another time?
- Is something wrong?
- I've been noticing lately...
No, I'm fine. Thank you. Thanks.
The second person I'm looking
into is Wheeler, her co-counselor.
Another ADA? Why?
Well, they dated
for a few months last year.
She broke things off,
and 40% of murders...
...involve some kind of
romantic relationship.
Also, Wheeler's divorced, one kid,
alimony, upside-down on his condo...
...career's stalled.
I asked. I can't get the time off.
Yeah, it is. It is a tough job.
But I can look out for myself,
you know that.
Listen, Mom, I... I know you haven't
been cashing the checks.
It's not charity, I'm your daughter.
I know. I know you worry about me.
I... I'm fine.
There's a third person
you're looking into?
Ex-convict named Charles Robinson.
Hansen and Wheeler prosecuted him
three years back, armed robbery.
Robinson wrote them love letters
from prison.
He's the first one
I'm gonna be looking into.
Robinson was released two months ago.
Hansen pulled his file last week.
Don't move.
I don't have much...
...but you're welcome to take
whatever you need.
I've been where you've been.
I don't think Robinson is our man.
He burned through a box of highlighters
on his King James Bible...
...none of it Old Testament.
- None of it Revelations.
- Fine. One down.
Hansen's on the move.
She's phoning county lockup,
arranging a meeting with Pope.
Alone.
Isn't my lawyer supposed
to be here?
I can call him, but the reason I'm here is
I don't think you murdered those people.
I think somebody else was in the house
when that 911 call was made.
Somebody who told you what was said,
which means you weren't there.
Is it somebody
you're trying to protect?
You're gonna help me? Is that it?
Where you from, Ohio?
I met DA's before,
you do a couple years of this...
...then try for a high-dollar job
at a law firm.
What happened, you get left behind?
I know a guy that'd put you to work
out on a corner.
Oh.
Close.
I grew up in Michigan. Brightmoor.
You know where that is?
I don't think you would've lasted
very long there, Lawrence.
I know what it's like
to want to get out of a place...
...so bad you'd be willing
to do almost anything.
And that's why I know, if you're gonna
take the fall for this...
...you must be very scared. Now...
...the person who knows what happened
must be somebody you care about.
Is it your younger brother Michael?
Pope's got a brother.
It's in his case file.
- Got it.
- Did he see the real killers?
You should leave this alone, lady.
I can do the time.
Figure I'll make amends for all the things
you never caught me on. Because I'm bad.
These people, they're evil.
Kill anyone they want.
They're protected. Keep asking,
they'll kill me and my brother.
- And probably you too.
- You can trust me.
We'll take care of you
and your brother.
If the killers are out there, I'm gonna
find them. It's my job. Now, why don't...?
Bitch, you keep your damn mouth shut
or I'll shut it for you.
I'm fine.
Okay. She's okay. She's okay.
Finch? You were right about Hansen.
Whoever framed Pope...
...will be coming after her, and only
Pope's brother knows who they are.
Hi, Mom. It's Jessica.
I'm just down in Mexico with Cindy,
and I'll be back tomorrow.
Okay? Talk soon. Bye.
Cindy?
- Yeah.
I look like a Cindy?
I didn't tell her about us yet.
It's been six months.
You haven't told your mom
you left your ex?
Maybe you're starting to think
you got a bum deal...
...trading an officer for an enlisted man.
I wish this weekend
could go on forever.
Already has.
It's Tuesday.
Which means you have to go back
to the base...
...and I'm not gonna see you again
for two weeks, which I hate.
Then ask me to stay.
I will.
I'll quit.
- I'll quit.
- Okay, then quit.
I already did.
- What?
- Yeah.
I didn't wanna take the chance...
...that you wouldn't be here
when I got back.
I've been training my whole life for
something that's never gonna happen.
Everybody's too damn rich
to go to war.
I'm obsolete and I love it.
Because it means I get to be with you.
I get my discharge in a month.
Then I'm gonna buy a boat.
And you get to be my first mate.
But first we need some more tequila.
Sweetheart, what's wrong? Jessica.
What's wrong?
Uh, it's New York. I don't know.
I don't know.
Something happened this morning.
- Is it a plane crash?
- I think it's two. I think it's two planes.
Thanks.
- You went to see Pope last night?
Yeah.
I gave him one more chance
to turn in his accomplice. Cut a deal.
- He give you anything?
No, as usual.
I'm, uh... I'm late.
She's trying to track down
Pope's brother.
He can ID the real killers.
And she's stonewalling Wheeler.
What, does she think he's involved?
Remember Pope said
they were protected from on high.
Wait a second.
Turns out there's a good reason
she doesn't trust Wheeler.
He might be working with the killers,
and they're after Michael Pope.
We better get to this kid
before someone else does.
Michael?
Can I talk to you for a second?
- I got a message from your brother.
- You don't know him.
Not exactly. I know what you saw.
I'm not the only one looking for you.
You need to come with me.
Hey. Hey. Help me.
Hey, this man is trying
to put me into a taxicab with him.
He's trying to take pictures of me.
- What's going on?
- How you doing?
- Michael Pope's still on the subway.
- Yeah.
When he comes up for air you can use
the GPS on your phone to find him.
If Pope's right about these guys,
I'm gonna need more than a cell phone.
About that,
I don't like firearms very much.
Neither do I.
But if someone has to have them...
...I'd rather it was me. Besides, my friend
from the subway has a line on some.
Lightly used. Steep discount.
Let's roll, let's roll
Let's rock, let's rock
Rock, roll
Hit the block
Let's roll, let's roll
Let's rock, let's rock
- Uh, what about this one?
- Are you planning on buying that one?
- I'm just...
- Put it back on the table...
...before somebody else
kicks your ass.
Have you guys seen the men's room?
Hey, Anton. Good to see you again.
You know this guy?
Wow, that's some pretty serious
equipment.
Have you guys taken a safety course?
Take you, for instance.
You're holding that thing sideways.
You can't aim it, and two, it'll eject
a shell casing right into your face. See?
I'm gonna hold on to these
while you guys get some more practice.
Have a nice day.
Who the hell was that?
All right, you're in.
Wheeler's got a secret file
on Hansen, Finch.
Old cases they worked together.
Sounds interesting. Pictures please.
Wait, wait, someone's coming.
It's Hansen.
Okay, now. You can go. Go, go, go.
Reese? I got a signal from your phone.
Tell me you found Michael Pope.
He's the only one
who knows who's after Hansen.
I found him, but somebody else
found him first. Listen.
Oh, Mikey. You were gonna tell him
all about us, weren't you? Hmm?
- Head uptown.
- Are you hearing this?
97th and Riverside. Step on it.
Gonna put a couple
in the back of his head.
Make it look like a gang thing.
You gotta do something.
Relax.
I'm on it.
Keep the change.
You're crazy. We're both dead now.
- Do you know who they are?
- I do now.
They're cops. Come on.
What exactly have you gotten me into?
I don't know. That's the whole point.
I hired you to help me figure that out.
Here.
I think we're up against
a group of corrupt cops.
I think their next target is Hansen.
But I don't know for certain.
I don't know anything...
...because you won't tell me where
you're getting your information.
When the towers came down,
you were in a hotel in Mexico.
I was here.
I was working.
Didn't know about the attacks
until that evening.
You see, Mr. Reese, until that day,
I had spent the better part of my life...
...making myself very rich.
Suddenly all that money
didn't seem to amount to much.
Do you have a phone?
Could you turn it off?
Let's walk.
Then I got a telephone call
from an old friend at the Pentagon.
After the attacks
the government gave itself the power...
...to read every e-mail,
listen to every cell phone.
But they needed something
that could sort through it all.
Something that could pick the terrorists
out of the population...
...before they could act.
They tried.
Able Danger, SpiNNaker, TIA.
But they were all failures.
Well, their biggest failure was bad PR.
The public wanted to be protected.
They just didn't wanna know
how they were.
So when they finally got a system
that worked, they kept it secret.
So how do you know about it?
I built it.
"Good with computers. " Remember?
But there was a problem
with this machine.
I had built it to prevent the next 9/11.
But it was seeing all sorts of crimes.
So I had to teach the machine
to divide the things it saw into two lists:
Relevant and irrelevant.
Events that would cause
massive loss of life were relevant.
So those would be passed along
to the NSA or the FBI.
And the irrelevant information?
Every night, at midnight,
the machine erases it.
It was only later
that I realized my mistake.
The whole point of Pandora's Box,
once you open it, you can't close it.
The idea of that irrelevant list...
...was eating away at me.
All those people with no idea
what was coming for them.
So where is the machine now?
What, the drives? Who knows?
A government facility somewhere.
But the machine?
The machine is everywhere.
Watching us with 10,000 eyes.
Listening with a million ears.
What did I tell you
about sending e-mails?
You could move in.
Never put anything in an e-mail
you cannot own.
You gave yourself a way
to communicate with it?
I was building the government
a tool of unimaginable power.
I thought maybe an off switch
would come in handy.
- So I built myself a backdoor into it.
- To access the irrelevant list.
Just a Social Security number.
If anyone ever found out,
I'd lose access. So nine digits.
That's all we get.
And we have no idea
why it picked Diane Hansen?
It wouldn't be steering us toward her
if it wasn't seeing something.
I don't know if I can protect Hansen.
I can't see the whole picture.
I offered you a job, Mr. Reese.
Never said it would be easy.
Hey, Carter.
- Yeah.
You hear about your pal Anton?
- No.
Him and his father tried to buy guns,
wound up getting shot.
- Are they dead?
Nope. Embarrassed.
They got taken out by one guy.
In a suit.
We've got all the parts.
Question is,
how do they all fit together?
Stills is narcotics.
Him and his men get word of deals.
They steal the drugs, the cash,
and kill all the witnesses.
Then they get Fusco to frame up guys
like Lawrence Pope for murder.
Exactly.
They've already killed five people.
- Six.
- What?
Lawrence Pope was stabbed to death
last night in his cell.
They're trying to cover their tracks.
They couldn't pull this off without
someone on the inside at the DA's office.
That's Wheeler. He's been spying on
Hansen and pulling their old case files.
Including the one for Robinson.
The same Robinson that sent Wheeler
and Hansen death threats from prison.
They looking for someone
they can frame like they framed Pope?
No, I think they found him.
But what do we do?
We stop them.
You wanted to meet?
Remsen and Avenue D
in Canarsie, 20 minutes.
Finch, it's happening now.
Hello?
Are you here?
You're gonna keep me waiting?
We don't have time.
What's your problem? Pope is dead.
His brother is gone, and we're still
searching for the clown who took him.
The problem is Wheeler, you idiot.
He knows.
He knows about Pope
and maybe some of the others.
We should have taken care of
this guy weeks ago.
I even found a shooter for you.
- Stop dragging your feet on this.
- How long do we have?
Twenty-four to 48 hours
before he goes to the DA, tops.
I can take care of the files at the office.
Take care of Wheeler. Tonight.
Hey, look what I found.
We've got ourselves a groupie.
Heavily armed too.
- You know this guy?
- No.
You're not law enforcement.
Cartel finally grow some stones?
Who the hell are you?
Concerned third party? Ha, ha.
He's alone, that's what he is,
so he doesn't matter.
Take care of him.
And, uh, get rid of Wheeler tonight.
Make it look clean.
Hey, Stills. You screw this up,
I won't let it get to me.
I'll take care of you
just like I took care of Pope.
I can look after myself.
You know that.
- Nice spot.
- It's Oyster Bay.
Glad you like it.
You're gonna be here
a long, long time.
I'm curious...
...was there a point where you knew
you'd become a bad guy?
I got a mortgage to pay,
same as everybody else.
I woke up one day
and I realized I gotta guard...
...these assholes on Wall Street
robbing everybody.
Stealing more than my annual salary
in an afternoon.
So I said, what the hell?
I don't believe you.
See, I've been watching you, Lionel...
...and I think there's a big difference
between you and your friends.
Your heart's not really into it.
Stills, he does it for money. But I think
you do it because you're loyal.
What's the difference?
It's why I'm gonna let you live.
Yeah. I'm considering sticking
around New York for a while.
If I do, I'm gonna need someone
on the inside.
And you might come in handy.
- So I'm working for you now?
- That's right.
But I've got two rules.
One, you so much as hurt anybody,
and I'll kill you.
I don't particularly like killing people,
but I'm very good at it.
And two, you have to be more careful.
For instance, if you're gonna
put someone in your car...
...you have to search them properly.
What the...?
What are you doing?
You have your vest on, officer?
Yeah.
- Where the hell have...?
There's no time.
We were wrong.
Hansen isn't the target.
She's the ringleader.
They're going after Wheeler.
Tonight.
Yo, Wheeler's up there.
He heads to the gym most nights.
I got Doyle upstairs.
Place is a dump. There's no doorman,
no cameras, nobody.
We'll take him in the lobby. Soon
as it's done, we take the shooter out.
Give him a block, take him out.
Head shots this time, understand?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Get our friend out of the trunk.
- Who is this guy?
Some ex-con Wheeler put away.
Azarello, lights.
- Doyle, talk to me.
- He's coming out now.
Come on, Henry, let's go.
- Wait.
- Remember that basketball game...
...we're supposed to go to?
- He's got his kid with him.
What a waste.
Better watch out.
You're a very bad man, Charles.
You're about to kill a man.
And his son.
Please. Please don't do this.
Drop your weapon.
I think that's true, actually.
You keep working on it,
you'll be able to throw that fast.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
Let him go.
I can't do that.
I let him go,
my friends and I go to jail.
Drag your friend outside
and take him to the hospital. Right now.
I think I kill you and your friend here.
Make it look like you killed each other.
Then, just because
you pissed me off...
...I'm going to kill your family,
and all your friends.
I don't have any friends.
I don't have any family left, either.
Left them all behind.
Went around the world
looking for bad guys.
But there were plenty of you,
right here, all along.
So now, essentially,
you're telling us you couldn't see...
...what was happening
in the parking lot at all.
- I'm done, Your Honor.
Ms. Hansen?
The state isn't paying you by the hour,
counselor.
Why don't we have the defendant
tell you in her own words?
Let's listen to the 911 call she made.
And, hey, take care of Wheeler, tonight.
Make it look clean. Stills,
you screw this up, I won't let it get to me.
I'll take care of you
just like I took care of Pope.
I can look after myself. You know that.
You ready to get to work, officer?
I'm no good to you. I'm dead.
Just a matter of time
before the gangs get me.
- Or IA.
- No one knows you're involved.
I took care of that.
Besides, they'll be too busy
looking for Stills.
The police'll think he's run for it.
The gangs and the mob
will think he's gone Witness Protection.
- Is that where he is, Witness Protection?
- No, Lionel.
He's in the trunk.
I gave him a choice and he chose wrong.
Only problem is, uh,
well, I had to shoot him with your gun.
You'd have a hard time
explaining that one.
So, ha, ha,
you'll be taking another trip.
But I'm not coming along this time.
- Where am I going?
- Oyster Bay.
Where no one's gonna find him
for a long, long time.
I'll be in touch.
You have a decision to make.
The machine gave you
another number.
The numbers never stop coming.
You should know that up front.
Two questions.
First...
...why me?
I've been watching you
for a long time, John.
We have more in common
than you might think.
The world thinks we're both dead,
for starters.
You said two questions.
You programmed the machine
to delete those irrelevant numbers.
But now you're trying to save them.
What changed your mind?
Let's just say you're not the only one
that's lost someone.
If you wanna leave, I'll give you
enough money to get as far as you need.
Disappear.
And if I stay?
They'll come looking for you.
The police, the mob,
your old friends at the CIA.
If you stay and we continue to do this...
...sooner or later,
both of us will probably wind up dead.
Actually dead, this time.
I said I'd tell you the truth.
I didn't say you'd like it.
Start talking, officer.
- You think I'm gonna rat on my friends?
Please, you can tell the DA
all about your crooked pals.
I wanna know about him,
the guy who came after you.
I don't know anything.
He was just some guy alone. In a suit.
You're gonna tell me everything
you don't know about him...
...and where I can find him.
Recast.AI, the collaborative platform
for building bots! https://recast.ai